http://www.rttsweb.com/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Search:
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies only to Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) collected by Real-Time Technology Solutions (“RTTS”, “we”, or “us”) during trial software registration or use or visitation to RTTS owned websites where this Privacy Policy is posted (the “Sites”) and does not apply to any other information collected by RTTS through any other means. If you have other agreements with RTTS governing products and services, then those agreements control privacy aspects between the respective organizations. RTTS’ Privacy Policy does not cover, or provide protection from, the activities of third parties.
This Privacy Policy answers the following questions:
1. What do we collect2. How do we collect it3. How do we use the information 4. How do you contact us or opt out
1. What do we collect
RTTS collects certain information when you register for a trial, request information, download a white paper, or when you use products or services. In registering with us or requesting information, you may provide us with your name, email address, title, company, industry, and other contact information. We may also collect your product registration information, product interest information, transaction information, or demographic information. For certain licensees, RTTS may require additional information, such as project and server information. We may collect payment information such as your credit card number and billing address if you purchase or license products and services from us. If you connect with RTTS accounts on third party social networking sites, we may also collect information about your social networking accounts, for example, your name, user name or handle, public profile, email address, and anything else you make publicly available on your social media profile.
Whenever you visit the Sites, RTTS may receive information on our server logs from your browser, including your computer's or mobile device's operating system and version, browser and language, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and geographic areas derived from your IP address, RTTS cookie information, file information, time stamped logs regarding access times and duration of visits, the websites you visited before coming to RTTS websites, and other usage data relating to your activities on our Sites, including the pages you request. We may relate this information to the PII you provide for purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
When you use our mobile apps, we also automatically collect information about your device and about your usage of and activity on our mobile apps. For example, we collect your device’s mobile operating system type and version, browser type, device type, geolocation data, Wi-Fi networking connection data, Internet Protocol (IP) address, device identifiers, time stamped logs regarding access times and duration of visits, and other information.
Certain third parties, including analytics companies, advertisers and ad networks, may also automatically collect information about you through our Sites, using cookies, Web beacons, and device identifiers, including personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites, devices, online channels and applications when you use our Sites.
2. How do we collect it:
User Input: Users provide us personal and business information on various forms throughout our Sites.
Cookies: By visiting our site cookies will be placed on your device (computer, mobile or tablet). A "cookie" is a small text file that is placed on your device by websites you visit. Some of the cookies we use are strictly necessary to operate our site.
IP Address: We and our analytics partners may use your IP address to determine your company name and geographic location.
3. How do we use the information:
We use PII collected through our Sites for purposes described in this Privacy Policy and as disclosed to you in connection with our Sites. For example, we may use your information to:
Provide and deliver products or services you’ve requested
Operate and improve our internal operations, systems, products, and services;
Understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience;
Provide customer and trial support of our product(s) and respond to other questions
Send you business and other pertinent information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
Communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and news about products and services offered by RTTS and our partners;
Enforce our terms and conditions or protect our business, partners, or users;
Protect against, investigate, and deter fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.
4. How do you contact us or opt out:
PII we collect may be retained for as long as needed to fulfill legitimate business purposes, including the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, or for a period of time specifically required or allowed by applicable regulations or laws.
Our marketing emails have a link to "opt-out" of receiving further marketing emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails related to your account, when applicable.
If you sign up for a trial and receive a subsequent email, you may reply to the email that you no longer wish to receive these emails.
You may also contact info@querysurge.com to let us know that you no longer wish to receive further marketing emails.
RTTS reserves the right to modify or update this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.
Looking for some more information?
We’re glad to help. (And with over 40 vendor-issued product certifications, your request is in good hands with us!) You can also email us directly at info@rttsweb.com
Consulting Services
Testing as a Service
Performance/Load Testing
Big Data Testing
Automated BI Report Testing
Expertise
Our Clients
Case Studies
Company
Why Choose RTTS?
The RTTS Team
Our Partners
Careers
Privacy Policy
©
Real-Time Technology Solutions, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
22 West 38th Street, 11th Floor, New York, NY 10018
Email: info@rttsweb.com | Phone: 212.240.9050
ip: 66.223.116.150
Strategy
Testing as a Service
Data Validation Assessment
Managed Testing Services
QA Process Assessment
DevOps / DevTest
Test Planning
QA Project Management
QA Project Sizing (Free service)
Implementation
Automated Functional Testing
Performance/Load Testing
Mobile Application Testing
Application Security Testing
JumpStart Program
Data Testing Solutions
General Data Testing
RTTS Data Testing Solutions
See how RTTS automates the data validation & testing of your Big Data, Data Warehouses, Data Migrations, ERP projects, & BI Reports LEARN MORE >>
Close
Courses
IBM
Micro Focus
Microsoft
Open Source
Data Warehouse Testing
Big Data Testing
Save Money - Training In The Cloud
Our live web-based training courses allow you to attend expert training courses with live instructors without leaving your office. LEARN MORE
Close
RTTS Products & Utilities
QuerySurge (External Site)
Custom Utilities
Automated Data Testing Solution
QuerySurge is the leading Data Testing solution specifically to automate the testing of Data Warehouses & Big Data go to QuerySurge web site>>
Close
Alliance Partners
Cloudera
Hortonworks
IBM
Micro Focus
Microsoft
MongoDB
Oracle
SAP
Teradata
Alliance Partners
Our alliance network features the leading technology & services firms in the world and, as an extension of our team, are integral in contributing to our success. Learn More >>
Close
Company Overview
Our Approach
The RTTS Team
Office Locations
Company History
Why Choose RTTS?
Awards
Clients
Careers
Positions at RTTS
Professional Growth
Training & Education
Company Benefits
Application & Interviewing Process
About RTTS
RTTS is the premier pure-play QA & Testing firm that specializes in Test Automation. RTTS has made over 600 companies successful since 1996. Learn More >>
Close
We appreciate your interest, and we'll contact you as soon as possible.
We appreciate your interest - you'll be receiving an email from us shortly.
